OK. And now here's a writing which is someone who maybe is a little confused. And again, I'm going to try and do it, but this is someone who is kind of disorderly.
As you can see, it's kind of all over the place.
There's lots of different types of form within it, indicates maybe a lack of balance.
OK, so that's what we call irregular.
Now there's another type of form which we refer to as natural and simplified, and this might be someone who tends to keep the letters separate, keeps the letters separate, and as you can see, it's just very simple.
It's a simplified type of writing.
And that again, is someone who, they're not pretentious, they don't have lots of flowery things, they're just a very natural, simple sort of person.
OK, and now we have a form that we call artistic or creative, and this is where they tend to kind of throw in little curly q's, like if they were saying, I am trying, they might go a little circle for the dot, as you can see this g, which looks a bit like an eight, that's a sign of artistic also.
And they tend to also do e's like that.
OK, so that's the artistic form, and now kind of an extension of that would be ornate, very ornate kind of person.
And that's someone who, they might be a little affected, or they might be someone who really likes to show themselves as somewhat more than they are.
Someone with lots of flourishes.
That kind of flourishy writing.
I'm sure you know someone who writes like that.
And also lots of embellishments and stuff, and they might also be putting lines under their writing.
As you can see we have seven distinct forms of writing and that's probably the first thing you'll going to be looking at when you're looking at someone's writing is the overall form of it.